free-webhosts.com 2011-05-29

# Privacy Policy for "Free Web Hosting" (Free-Webhosts.com)

**Free Web Hosting Directory (Free-Webhosts.com) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This statement covers how we use any info that may be collected about our visitors.**

**General**  
We (Free-Webhosts.com) do NOT collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us.  
We do NOT provide or sell personal info such as the names, addresses, or email addresses of our visitors to anyone else.  
We do NOT send unsolicited email to you (Spam).

**Contact Forms**  
Any info submitted by contact forms is optional. If email addresses are given for us to reply to, these will not be shared with anyone else. If you wish to not be contacted, you may leave the name and email address fields blank to send an anonymous comment.

**User reviews**  
Free-Webhosts.com user reviews and ratings pages collect the IP addresses of visitors who post messages to prevent abuse. The first two of the 4 parts of your IP address are posted with your message, which may give an idea of what country you are in. The IP addresses of abusers may be banned from further postings. Any info that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Therefore you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your email address or any personal information. We reserve the right to delete or edit the content of any message in order to remove offensive content or to improve readability and usefullness. We are not responsible for the postings of other visitors.

**Advertisers (Third-party ads)**  
Free-Webhosts.com may display ads for other companies' websites to support our web site. Some of the advertisements on this website may use technology such as cookies and web beacons, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information such as your IP address, your ISP, the browser type you used to visit our website, and in some cases, whether or not you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (for example, showing ads pertaining to local services in your country or location) or showing certain ads based on specific sites previously visited (such as showing image hosting service ads to someone who frequents imagehosting websites). We do not have access to this collected information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Free-Webhosts.com and its advertisers (such as Google) may set and access cookies on your computer. Google's use of their DART cookie enables it to serve ads to website users based on their visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing info about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Free-Webhosts.com website. You can set your browser to not accept cookies (or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security). See your browser's documentation for more information on accepting cookies. By setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once to leave user reviews, thus saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user may be limited in some areas of the Free-Webhosts.com website, such as not being able to submit user reviews. Cookies also may be used for statistical purposes, to remember user preferences, or to rotate ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the "Google ad and content network privacy policy", which you can read at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Statistical Tracking**  
Free-Webhosts.com uses a statistical tracker to analyze trends and traffic to this website. The tracker does not collect any personal info, but only collects aggregate data. This general statistics data may be given to select advertisers to verify the amount of traffic to this website. The tracker may make use of cookies to recognize repeated visits by a visitor for statistical purposes.

**External Links**  
This website contains numerous links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other websites.

**Assent, and Changes to this Policy**  
By using this website, you signify your assent to the Free-Webhosts.com privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting such changes on this web page, so please check this web page periodically for changes. If you do not agree to the current private policy, please do not use this website.

**Contacting Us**  
See our contact page.
